<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="title_pref_tutorial" msgid="3245369379022519951">"Launch \"Explore by touch\" tutorial"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_title" msgid="3604139189214645351">"Accessibility tutorial"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_next" msgid="5403131568391761625">"Next"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_back" msgid="7953265962480572962">"Previous"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_finish" msgid="8651842380314324443">"Finish"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_skip" msgid="4635703249458449485">"Exit"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_touch_disabled" msgid="1947871282831171107">"Touch disabled while tutorial is speaking"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_title" msgid="8913174159810078422">"Lesson 1: Exploring the screen"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_1" msgid="6281024124325477313">"When Explore by Touch is turned on, you can touch the screen to learn what\'s under your finger. For example, the current screen contains app icons. Find one of them by touching the screen and sliding your finger around."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_2_more" msgid="7154137274310772436">"Good. Keep sliding your finger around the screen until you find at least one more icon."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_3" msgid="5866504456242703872">"You can also explore by swiping your finger left and right anywhere on the screen. Try quickly swiping from left to right to move to the next icon."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_4" msgid="56981537955090208">"To activate something that you\'ve explored, tap the screen twice. Explore until you find the <xliff:g id="APP_NAME">%1$s</xliff:g> icon. Then double-tap anywhere on the screen to activate it."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_5" msgid="1208294090974872449">"You found the <xliff:g id="APP_NAME">%1$s</xliff:g> icon. Double-tap anywhere on the screen to activate the icon."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_5_exited" msgid="8862005898053070331">"You explored past the <xliff:g id="APP_NAME_0">%1$s</xliff:g> icon. Try exploring the screen until you find the <xliff:g id="APP_NAME_1">%1$s</xliff:g> icon again."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_1_text_6" msgid="4094982888777210681">"To move to the next lesson, find the <xliff:g id="NEXT">%1$s</xliff:g> button, located near the bottom-right corner of the screen, then double-tap to activate it."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_title" msgid="8237242914117751937">"Lesson 2: Scrolling through lists"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_1" msgid="3701529365516687824">"To scroll through a list, you can slide two fingers along the screen. For example, the current screen contains a list of app names that can scroll up or down. First, try to explore the screen and identify an app."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_2" msgid="6798295786754555066">"Now place two fingers on an item in the list and slide both fingers up. If you reach the top of the screen, lift your fingers, place them lower on the list, and continue sliding up."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_3" msgid="3159628036244792602">"Explore the screen to find one more app."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_4" msgid="8714551968743323879">"You can also scroll an entire page by swiping your finger. To scroll to the next page, swipe right then left using a single motion. Try to scroll to the next page by swiping right then left."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_5" msgid="8943035012040524546">"Explore the screen again to find an app in the current page."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_6" msgid="6541093467485133324">"Swiping the opposite direction, left then right in a single motion, will move to the previous page. Try to scroll to the previous page by swiping left then right."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_2_text_7" msgid="3684610203615874623">"To move to the next lesson, find the <xliff:g id="NEXT">%1$s</xliff:g> button, located near the bottom-right corner of the screen, then double-tap to activate it."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_title" msgid="6024010587544294119">"Lesson 3: Context menus"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_1" msgid="9044343256290855911">"TalkBack has two context menus that make it easy to find settings and controls: the Global Context Menu and the Local Context Menu. You can activate a menu item by sliding your finger around the circle of menu items and releasing when you hear the desired item. Try bringing up the Global Context Menu by swiping your finger <xliff:g id="GLOBAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%1$s</xliff:g> in a single motion."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_2" msgid="2357293277631473840">"The Global Context Menu contains general commands that work everywhere throughout TalkBack. Try to read all the text on the screen by pressing on the centre of the screen to bring up a circular menu around your finger, and then sliding your finger around the circle of options until you hear \"<xliff:g id="READ_FROM_TOP_ITEM_TEXT">%1$s</xliff:g>.\""</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_3_hidden" msgid="8766520681673257029">"You closed the Global Context Menu. Try bringing up the Global Context Menu again by swiping your finger <xliff:g id="GLOBAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%1$s</xliff:g> in a single motion."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_3" msgid="2904044424555349808">"Good. That command will read all of the items on the screen. In addition to a Global Context Menu, TalkBack also has a Local Context Menu. The Local Context Menu contains controls that change based on what item on the screen you have selected. Try bringing up the Local Context Menu by swiping your finger <xliff:g id="LOCAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%1$s</xliff:g> in a single motion."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_4" msgid="2111031135741866859">"Pressing your finger down in the centre of the screen and then lifting it will cancel and close the menu. Try closing the Local Context Menu now."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_3_text_5" msgid="7941017643852409">"You now know how to bring up and navigate through the context menus. You will learn more about when to use the context menus in the following lesson. Find and activate the <xliff:g id="NEXT">%1$s</xliff:g> button near the bottom-right corner of the screen to move to the next lesson."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_title" msgid="3898999689844982160">"Lesson 4: Reading granularities"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_1" msgid="9109984626149104730">"TalkBack has granularity controls that give you different ways to navigate through text. For example, you can read text paragraph by paragraph, word by word or even character by character. To get started, find the text box in the centre of the screen to read its content."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_2" msgid="2135471055480731456">"Focusing an item will read all of its text at the default level of granularity. Try changing the granularity to read this text one character at a time. First, swipe your finger <xliff:g id="LOCAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%1$s</xliff:g> to bring up the Local Context Menu."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_3_focus_lost" msgid="8713408442068375091">"You navigated away from the target text box. Try tapping on the centre of the screen to navigate back to the text box."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_3" msgid="5978230561116221609">"Good. Now, slide your finger around the menu until you hear <xliff:g id="CHARACTER_GRANULARITY">%1$s</xliff:g>, then select it."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_4_menu_hidden" msgid="879065229665819294">"You closed the Local Context Menu without changing to <xliff:g id="CHARACTER_GRANULARITY">%1$s</xliff:g>. Swipe your finger <xliff:g id="LOCAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%2$s</xliff:g> to bring up the Local Context Menu again."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_4" msgid="2648520368832903832">"Good. You are now navigating by character granularity. Swiping from the top of the screen to the bottom of the screen will move forward by one character. Try swiping from the top of the screen to the bottom of the screen 3 times to read the next 3 characters of the text."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_5_granularity_changed" msgid="124123881203918192">"You changed the granularity so that it is no longer <xliff:g id="CHARACTER_GRANULARITY_0">%1$s</xliff:g>. You can change back to <xliff:g id="CHARACTER_GRANULARITY_1">%1$s</xliff:g> from the Local Context Menu by swiping your finger <xliff:g id="LOCAL_CONTEXT_MENU_GESTURE_DIRECTION">%2$s</xliff:g> in a single motion."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_5" msgid="5408515769417809079">"You now know how to change the reading granularity and read text. This concludes the TalkBack tutorial. To exit the tutorial, find and activate the <xliff:g id="FINISH">%1$s</xliff:g> button, located near the bottom-right corner of the screen."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_lesson_4_text_view_text" msgid="6855162251486030701">"This is some example text that you can read at different granularities."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_alert_dialog_exit" msgid="6604033839776950241">"Exit"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_service_inactive_title" msgid="5640949274947370358">"Explore by Touch Required"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_service_inactive_message" msgid="1808749405557397970">"This tutorial requires Explore by touch. Please turn TalkBack on and enable Explore by Touch before launching the tutorial."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_service_suspended_title" msgid="7163740223497398638">"TalkBack Suspended"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_service_suspended_message" msgid="5633367032537299661">"The TalkBack tutorial is not available while feedback is paused. Please resume TalkBack feedback and relaunch the tutorial to continue."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_missing_assignment_title" msgid="5676431029357436455">"Missing gesture assignment"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tutorial_missing_assignment_message" msgid="2845312981319504607">"There is no gesture assigned to the \"<xliff:g id="ACTION">%1$s</xliff:g>\" action. Please visit TalkBack Settings to set a shortcut gesture for that action, and then relaunch the TalkBack tutorial."</string>
</resources>
